Karel Nagel



karel789@hotmail.com



linkedin.com/in/karelnagel



56638788



https://github.com/karelnagel

Summary

Hi, I am 22 year old software developer from Estonia, I am studying IT in the University of Tartu. I currently have around 3 years of programming experience and about a year of working experience. I have worked on two companies as a Backend developer and as a Tech lead. I worked there with the following technologies: ASP.NET Core backend, MySQL database, ReactJS, Java Spring backend, Flutter app and more.

I have been an investor in different blockchain technologies since 2017, but when the NFT boom hit this summer, then I really realized what web3 and Ethereum really means for the world. Since then I have been actively learning about the technology and trying to create some projects myself.

Projects that I have made and am most proud of:

Creature Game - a dapp that I made to get more familiar with Solidity development and publishing a dapp. It is a game where you have to match user twitter handle with their Creature NFT image and if you collect all the NFTs, then you can leave your message to the website, get the final NFT and get to burn other unneccesary NFTs. It's live in Polygon mainnet.

https://creature-game.web.app/

CarWatch - a web2 website that gathers together car sales from different car auction sites and users can search for cars. Also users can save searches and when a new sale comes it will be sent to user in Messenger. It is built with Java Spring Boot and React.

https://github.com/karelnagel/autopood

MT5 No Nonsense Forex backtester - a forex bot that makes backtesting and trading much easier and faster. It is currently for sale for 59\$. It is written in MQL5 and the website is made with WordPress. https://mt5.kareInagel.com/

Experience



Technical Lead

Fudler

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021 (4 months)



Back End Developer

Tinksmat Systems OÜ Nov 2020 - Jul 2021 (9 months)

Education



University of Tartu Institute of Computer Science

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology 2020 - 2024

Kuperjaanovi JVP

2019 - 2020

Võru Gümnaasium

2016 - 2019

Võru Kesklinna Kool

2007 - 2016

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • C# • Flutter • MQL4 • Java • ASP.NET • Git • JavaScript • web3.js • Smart Contracts